{
    "subject": "Luis_Bay\u00f3n_Herrera",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Buenos_Aires_a_la_vista",
    "human_readable": "Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera created Buenos Aires a la vista.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8454030156135559,
            "question": "Who created the artwork 'Buenos Aires a la vista'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8343356847763062,
            "question": "When was 'Buenos Aires a la vista' created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7044605612754822,
            "question": "Where can you find 'Buenos Aires a la vista'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6541334390640259,
            "question": "Where was Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6126511096954346,
            "question": "What inspires the artwork 'Buenos Aires a la vista'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6086288094520569,
            "question": "What kind of artwork is 'Buenos Aires a la vista'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.600504457950592,
            "question": "Is Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera known for creating other artworks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5752385854721069,
            "question": "What is the title of the artwork created by Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5330572724342346,
            "question": "What are some of the techniques used in 'Buenos Aires a la vista'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5047079920768738,
            "question": "What is the overall message or theme conveyed by 'Buenos Aires a la vista'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera created Buenos Aires a la vista.",
            "html": "yago_12698_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the techniques used in 'Buenos Aires a la vista'?",
            "html": "yago_12698_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of the artwork created by Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera?",
            "html": "yago_12698_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera known for creating other artworks?",
            "html": "yago_12698_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12698_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12698_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12698_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12698_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12698_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12698_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12698_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12698_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12698_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12698_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple \"Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera created Buenos Aires a la vista\". The document with file path \"/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_12698/re-ranker-msmarco/47.txt\" mentions that \"Buenos Aires a la vista is a 1950 Argentine musical drama film directed and written by Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera...\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera directed and wrote the film \"Buenos Aires a la vista\" (1950). Therefore, it is accurate to say that Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera created the film \"Buenos Aires a la vista.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}